我们游览的终点站是
And as we conclude the tour...
吼吼吼  这个景点太稀有了
Ooh hoo hoo, this is a rare sight.
丽芙·鲁尼的亲爹啊
Liv rooney's real-life father.
别打扰他
Don't disturb him.
我们从后门出去
We'll go out the back.
才没门呢
No way.
我买的是全票
I was promised a full tour.
我的贺卡上要印上我在这里
My holiday card will have a picture of me
每个房间拍的照片
In every room in this house.
好吧
Fine.
请稍等片刻
Just wait here one second.
顺便说一句  我恨死你了
Also, I hate you.
你好啊  老爸
Hey, pops.
你在忙乎什么呢
Whatcha up to?
我去五金店的时候
While I was at the hardware store,
顺便买了个报警系统
I picked up an alarm system.
我们家里有个大明星
We have a celebrity living in this house.
会有人花钱来参观的
People would pay to get in here.
赞  给我好好讲讲吧
Fascinating. show me everything.
别将目光从操作板上移开
Don't take your eyes off this box.
我从来没像今天这样对你在干的活这么感兴趣
I've never been more interested in anything you've ever done.
别动啊  乔伊
Hold still, joey.
我在设置动作探测器
I'm setting the motion detector.
任何动作都会触发报警器
Any movement will trip the alarm.
警报启动
Alarm activated.
检测到 12 个入侵者
12 intruders detected.
这到底是什么破玩意
What's wrong with this thing?
呃  我知道咋回事了
Well-- well, I know.
我太激动了  动作根本停不下来
Just so excited I can't stand still.
警报取消
Alarm deactivated.
屋内安全
house secure.
我好像之前跟你们说过把那些吓人的玩意
I thought I told you to put those creepy things
放回到阁楼里去
Back up in the attic.
我记得我好像放过了
I thought I did.
你总不会认为它们是自己闹鬼走到这里来的吧
You don't think they came down on their own, do you?